{
    "id": "bacdbba1c8914c2b80706e1f0da1ccd6",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "All the members of the family have a rightful claim to the ...................... property.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ancient",
                "ancestral",
                "ancestry"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The vehicle was badly damaged but the driver escaped .....................…",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "miracle",
                "miraculous",
                "miraculously"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The village woman looked at the crowds and the traffic in .....................…",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bewilder",
                "bewilderment",
                "bewildered"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I visit Canada .....................… to meet my sister.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "occasion",
                "occasional",
                "occasionally"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The minister gave a …………………. reply to his detractors.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "befit",
                "befitted",
                "befitting"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Nehru’s ………………….. with Gandhi helped him change his views.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "associate",
                "associative",
                "association"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Great leaders ..................... people even after they are gone.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "inspire",
                "inspiration",
                "inspirational"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t think there is any ………………… for you to come again.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "necessary",
                "necessity",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He was very ....................... about the project.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "enthusiasm",
                "enthusiastic",
                "enthusiastically"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "His ....................... with politics affected his career.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "preoccupy",
                "preoccupation",
                "preoccupational"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}